(Sheldon:)I recently read
that during World War Two,
(Sheldon:)Joseph Stalin had
a research program
(Sheldon:)to create
supersoldiers
(Sheldon:)by having women
impregnated by gorillas.
(Howard:)What a sick use
of science.
(Raj:)Hey, as long as
the baby's healthy.
(Amy:)I wonder if Stalin considered
any other animals.
(Leonard:)Hippos are
the deadliest creature.
(Leonard:)A half-human, half-hippo soldier
would be pretty badass.
(Howard:)Yes, but when they're
hungry-hungry,
(Howard:)you can stop them
with marbles.
(Sheldon:)Yeah, the correct animal
(Sheldon:)for interspecies supersolider
is koala.
(Sheldon:)You would wind up with an army
so cute it couldn't be attacked.
(Raj:)But half-man, half-owl
could fly...
(Sheldon:)The answer is cuddly soldiers
with big flat noses. Moving on.
(Howard:)So, Penny, when's
the new job start?
(Penny:)Next Monday.
(Bernadette:)Did you get a chance
to look over
(Bernadette:)the materials I gave you?
(Penny:)Uh, not yet,
but I will.
(Bernadette:)Great. When?
(Penny:)I said I'll get to it.